sazainvestments.com 2010-01-27

# Saza Investments | Privacy Policy

**From the moment you open an  account with Saza Investments, we do everything to protect your privacy.**

**Our Commitment to your Privacy**

Saza Investments have always been committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity, and security of personal information about our current and prospective customers. We are proud of our privacy practices and want you to know how we protect this information and use it to service your account.

We hope you will take a moment to review the full privacy policy of Saza Investments. Please note that certain details of this policy may depend on whether you deal with us through an investment professional, your employer, or directly as an individual investor. The privacy policies of Saza Investments is reviewed annually. Our printed and online notices are then updated to reflect any material changes.

You do not have to contact us to benefit from Saza Investments' privacy protections; they apply automatically to all of our clients.

**Saza Investments Investments Privacy Policy**

 **How and Why We Obtain Personal Information  
**Saza Investments takes great care to protect your personal information, and when we use it, we do so with respect for your privacy. We may use personal information about you to develop, offer, and deliver products and services; process transactions in your account; respond to inquires from you or your representative; or to fulfill legal and regulatory requirements. Saza Investments may collect public and nonpublic personal information about you from any of the following sources: 

  * You or your representative on applications or forms (for example, name, address, Passport number, birth date, assets, and income)

  * Transactional activity in your account (for example, investing history and balances)

  * Other interactions with Saza Investments (for example, discussions with our customer service staff or information you enter into our Web sites)

  * Information services and consumer reporting agencies (for example, to verify your identity or to better understand your product and service needs)

  * You or your representative regarding your preferences (for example, paper statements vs. electronic statements, or the screen layout you specify if you use our Internet sites)

**How We Protect Your Information**  
Saza Investments has always considered the protection of sensitive information to be a foundation of customer trust and a sound business practice. We employ extensive physical, electronic and procedural controls, and we regularly adapt these controls to respond to changing requirements and advances in technology. Within Saza Investments and among our service providers, we restrict access to personal information to those who require it to provide products and services to you. We may share the personal information that we collect with the following entities:

  * Saza Investments corporate affiliates including internal service providers (for example, our data processing company and printing operation)

  * Unaffiliated service providers (for example, printing and mailing companies, securities clearinghouses, and other entities who may provide services at Saza Investments' direction)

  * Other organizations, with your consent or as directed by your representative (for example, if you use Saza Investments as a financial reference)

  * Other organizations, as permitted by law (for example, for fraud prevention)

  * As described below, in circumstances that apply only to certain subsets of Saza Investments customers Information collected from investment professionals’ customers is not shared with Saza Investments affiliates for marketing purposes, except with the consent of the investment professional or the client.

**Privacy Online**  
Privacy, security and service in our online operations are just as critical as in the rest of our business. Saza Investments employs all of the safeguards described previously, along with the following Internet-specific practices. We make extensive use of firewall barriers, encryption techniques and authentication procedures to maintain the security of your online session and to protect Saza Investments accounts and systems from unauthorized access. We may also place cookies and similar files on your hard drive for security purposes, to facilitate site navigation, and to personalize your experience on our site. Our cookies do not identify you by name as an individual or by account number.

When you visit Saza Investments' Internet site, we may collect technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, Internet protocol address, pages visited, and average time spent on our Web sites. This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve our Web design and functionality.

**Your Connection to Saza Investments**  
You may interact with us in various ways, and when you do, we may exchange information with parties in addition to those described above. For example, if you conduct business with Saza Investments through your employer or investment professional, we may exchange the information we collect with them, or with others at their direction.

If you interact with Saza Investments directly as an individual investor, we may exchange information about you with our affiliates to offer Saza Investments products and services, only as permitted by law. Saza Investments does not share personal information about our customers with third parties for use in their marketing.
